No man left behind.
Land of Bad is a action, war, thriller film directed by William Eubank.
When a Delta Force special ops mission goes terribly wrong, Air Force drone pilot Reaper
has 48 hours to remedy what has devolved into a wild rescue operation.
With no weapons and no communication other than the drone above, the ground mission
suddenly becomes a full-scale battle when the team is discovered by the enemy.
Kinney, played by Liam Hemsworth.
Reaper, played by Russell Crowe.
Abel, played by Luke Hemsworth.
Bishop, played by Ricky Whittle.
Sugar, played by Milo Ventimiglia.
Staff Sgt. Nia Branson, played by Chika Ikogwe.
Land of Bad is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by William
Eubank, who co-wrote the script with David Frigerio.
The film stars Liam Hemsworth, Russell Crowe, Luke Hemsworth, Ricky Whittle, and Milo Ventimiglia, and
follows a US Army Delta Force team on a rescue operation that comes under attack from terrorists.
Land of Bad was released theatrically on February 16, 2024.
It grossed $7 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of air force, battle, behind
enemy lines, special ops, rescue operation.
The tone is intense.